[Music]
[音乐]
this is nick with logosbynic.com and in
我是logosbynic.com的尼克
this tutorial we'll be going over how
在本教程中，我们将介绍
you can create simple animated gifs
您可以创建简单的动画gif
using inkscape
使用Inkscape
now unfortunately inkscape doesn't allow
不幸的是，Inkscape不允许
you to export animated gifs so what
您要导出动画gif，那又如何
we're going to do is we're going to
我们要做的是我们要
create the frames individually and then
逐个创建框架，然后
open them as layers in and then
在中以层的形式打开它们，然后
from there we can export as an animated
从那里我们可以将其作为动画输出
gif and if you don't know what is
GIF，如果你不知道什么是
it's a free and open source image editor
这是一个免费的开源图片编辑器
i'll have a link to that in the
我会在
description of the video if you want to
视频描述(如果您想要
download and install that real quick and
下载并安装该应用程序
then you'll be good to get started
然后你就可以开始了
so for my example here as you can see i
在我的例子中，如你所见，我
have this little animated character that
有一个小小的动画角色
i create we have some
我创造了我们有一些
basic facial movements going on here and
基本的面部动作在这里进行，
then we have a sleeping cat on the desk
然后我们在桌子上放了一只睡着的猫
with his tail occasionally moving and
他的尾巴偶尔会动一下，
the way that i made this was i created
我做这个的方式是我创造的
these frames individually here in
这些帧在这里单独显示
inkscape
墨迹
and what i did was i used the batch
我所做的就是我用了这批
export feature to export all of these
导出功能以导出所有这些内容
individual images and then open them
单个图像，然后打开它们
with and then from there i was able
从那时起，我就能
to quickly export it so i'm going to
为了快速出口它，所以我要
show you how to do something similar
向你展示如何做类似的事情
maybe not with this particular design
也许不是这种特殊的设计
i'm going to show you how to create like
我将向您展示如何像这样创建
a simple loading spinner design so let's
一个简单的加载旋转器设计，所以让我们
open up a new document here and get
在此处打开新文档并获取
started now i should mention that you
从现在开始，我应该提到你
should be using inkscape version 1.2 or
应使用Inkscape 1.2版或
later in order to follow along with this
后来为了跟上这一步
tutorial because we're going to need the
教程，因为我们将需要
batch export feature which is new to
新增的批量导出功能
this version if you don't know which
这个版本，如果你不知道哪个版本
version you're using just go to help and
您正在使用的版本只需转到帮助和
about inkscape
关于Inkscape
and it should tell you right there as
它应该会在那里告诉你
you can see i'm using version 1.2 or
您可以看到我使用的是1.2版或
version 1.2.1 to be specific so as long
版本1.2.1具体而言，只要
as you're using this version or later
当您使用此版本或更高版本时
you'll be good to go
你就可以走了
so i'm going to press 1 on the keyboard
所以我要按键盘上的1键
to zoom in to 100
放大到100的步骤
and i'm going to press down the mouse
我要按下鼠标
wheel and move the mouse to get the uh
滚轮并移动鼠标即可获得
canvas off of the page here we're
画布从页面上下来，我们在这里
actually not going to use this canvas at
实际上我不会用这张画布
all we're going to create rectangles and
我们要做的就是创造长方形和
use those for our frames so i'm going to
把它们用在我们的镜框上，所以我要
grab the
抓起
rectangle tool the squares and
矩形工具的正方形和
rectangles tool and i'm going to create
矩形工具和我要创建的
a
一个
vertical rectangle like that
像这样的垂直矩形
maybe a little smaller and i'm going to
也许再小一点，我就会
use this handle right here to give this
就在这里用这个把手给这个
a rounded edge we want this to be all
我们想要的就是这一切
the way around it like that
像这样绕过它的方式
and i'm going to make this a lighter
我要把这个做得更轻
shade of gray maybe something like that
灰色的阴影，也许是这样的
now i'll grab the selection tool
现在我要拿起选择工具
i'm going to duplicate this by right
我正要把这个复制一下
clicking it and going to duplicate and
点击它并复制和
then i'm going to move this down but i'm
然后我要把这个往下移，但我
also going to hold ctrl on my keyboard
我也要按住键盘上的ctrl键
while i move it like that so it locks it
当我像那样移动它时，它就会锁定它
onto the vertical axis and now we have
到垂直轴上，现在我们有了
these two rectangles i'm going to click
我要点击的这两个矩形
and drag over both of those i'm going to
然后拖过我要去的那两个
group them together by going to object
通过转到Object将它们组合在一起
and selecting group
和选择组
and now if i click on this object as you
现在如果我像你一样点击这个物体
can see here we have these scaling
可以看到这里我们有这些比例
handles represented by these arrows if i
如果I，这些箭头表示的句柄
click on this again you'll notice it
再次点击这个，你就会注意到它
toggles between the scaling handles and
在缩放手柄和
the rotation handles with this rotation
使用此旋转处理的旋转
handle selected i'm just going to click
手柄被选中，我只需点击
and drag it like this and then i'm going
像这样拖着它，然后我就走
as i hold the ctrl key it's locking it
当我按住Ctrl键时，它正在锁定它
onto 15 degree increments so i'm going
到15度的增量，所以我要
to start right here and while holding
从这里开始，同时按住
control and while holding the click i'm
控件，并在按住单击的同时
going to press the space bar to make a
我要按空格键来做一个
copy and i'm going to move this over to
收到，我要把这个移到
the right one two three
右边的一二三
press the space bar again one two three
再次按空格键1、2、3
space bar again one two three and for
空格键再次为一、二、三和
this last one you can just let go and
最后一个你可以放手，然后
there you go now we have the individual
好了，现在我们找到个人了
rectangles for our spinner so let me
长方形为我们的旋转器，所以让我
click and drag over all of this right
单击并拖动到所有这些右侧
here and let me go to object
在这里，让我去反对
ungroup
解组
click off of the graphic to deselect
单击图形以取消选择
everything let me just center this up
每件事都让我把这个放在中心
here again to move the page around you
再次在这里移动页面围绕您
just press down the mouse wheel and move
只需按下鼠标滚轮并移动
the mouse i'm going to click on this top
我要点击这个顶部的鼠标
one right here and i'm going to make
就在这里，我要做一个
this a darker shade like that
这个是像那样深一点的色调
and now i'm going to click and drag over
现在我要点击并拖动到
all of this and now i want to group it
所有这些，现在我想将其分组
together by going to object
一起去反对
group
群组
and let me actually just scale this down
实际上，让我来缩小一下规模
a little bit click and drag this to
稍微点击一下，然后将其拖动到
scale it down and then i'm going to hold
把它缩小，然后我要拿着
ctrl and shift to make this a little
按住Ctrl和Shift键可以让它变得有点
smaller
更小的
so i want that to be a little smaller
所以我想要小一点的
like that and now i'm going to create a
就像这样，现在我要创建一个
rectangle going over it or a square
越过它的矩形或正方形
rather i'm going to click and drag hold
相反，我要点击并拖动按住
ctrl to make a perfectly symmetrical
按Ctrl键可创建完美对称的
square like that we don't want rounded
像这样的正方形，我们不想要圆角
corners on this one so i'm going to
这张照片的边角所以我要
click on this little corner box up here
点击这里的这个小角框
that says make corner sharp
那就是说让角落变得锋利
and i will make this one white this is
我会把这个做成白色的这是
going to represent the background of our
将代表我们的背景
design so let me grab the select tool
设计，让我抓起选择工具
let me lower this to the bottom this
让我把这个降到最低
button right here that says lower
按钮就在这里，上面写着更低
selection to the bottom
选择到底部
and now i'm going to click and drag over
现在我要点击并拖动到
both of these objects and i want to make
这两件物品和我想要制作的
sure that that it's centered up
确保它位于中心位置
vertically and horizontally so i'm going
垂直和水平，所以我要去
to open up the alignment menu which is
要打开对齐菜单，请执行以下操作
right here the keyboard shortcut is ctrl
在这里，键盘快捷键是ctrl
shift a so i'm just going to use that
换班a，所以我要用它
instead ctrl shift a
相反，Ctrl Shift a
where it says relative to make sure you
它说的是相对的，以确保你
have last selected enabled and we're
上一次选择了启用，我们正在
going to center this up on the vertical
把这个放在垂直的中心
axis and the horizontal axis like that
轴和水平轴就像这样
and i actually don't like the contrast
我其实不喜欢这种对比
here i'd like this to be a little darker
这里我想把这件颜色调深一点
so i'm just going to grab the edit paths
所以我只需要抓取编辑路径
by nodes tool and click on that one
按节点工具，然后单击该工具
object right there and i'm going to
就在那里反对，我要
choose a darker shade
选择较深的色调
there we go that looks a little better
我们走吧，看起来好一点了
okay click off of the deselect so what i
好的，点击取消选择，那么我
want to do is i basically want to create
我想做的就是我基本上想要创造
copies of this for each frame of this i
此文件的每一帧的复印件
want each of these rectangles to be
希望这些矩形中的每个都是
highlighted in this color in separate
单独以此颜色突出显示
frames so let me select this right here
框架，所以让我在这里选择这个
let me press ctrl d to duplicate it
让我按ctrl d来复制它
hold ctrl move it over to the right like
按住Ctrl键将其移到右侧，如下所示
this and now we have our second frame
现在我们有了我们的第二帧
so i want to rotate this around i'm
所以我想把这个旋转一下，我是
going to click on this object
在此对象上单击
click on it again to get the rotation
再次点击即可获得旋转
handles and i'm going to hold ctrl i'm
把手，我要按住Ctrl键我是
going to rotate this
我要把这个旋转一下
three steps to the right like that so
向右走三步，就是这样
now we have another copy of this object
现在我们有了该对象的另一个副本
where this rectangle is illuminated
在此矩形被照亮的位置
instead of this one
而不是这个
and if you can see where i'm going with
如果你能看清我的意图
this i'm going to create more copies for
我将为此创建更多副本
every single one of these rectangles so
这些矩形中的每一个都是
let me zoom out here to zoom in and out
让我在这里缩小以放大和缩小
i'm just holding ctrl and rolling up and
我只是按住Ctrl键然后卷起来
down the mouse wheel let me create
按下鼠标滚轮让我创建
another copy of this
另一份副本
ctrl d
Ctrl%d
hold control move it over like that
按住控制键，像这样把它移过去
click off of it to deselect
单击该选项以取消选择
click on the object
单击该对象
click on it again to get the rotation
再次点击即可获得旋转
handles
手柄
and then hold ctrl
然后按住Ctrl键
one two three and there we go now we
一、二、三，现在我们开始吧
have that one so i'll show you this one
有那个吗，我给你看这个
more time i'm going to click and drag
更多的时间我会点击并拖拽
over it
在它上面
ctrl d to duplicate
要复制的Ctrl%d
hold ctrl move this over here
按住Ctrl键，把这个移到这里
click off of it deselect
单击该选项取消选择
click on just this object right here
仅在此处单击此对象
click on it again to get the rotation
再次点击即可获得旋转
handles hold control
手柄保持控制
one two three there we go and what i'll
一，二，三，我们走，我要做的是
do is i'll just fast forward through
我要做的就是快进
this real quick
这真的很快
okay so as you can see i have finished
好的，如你所见，我已经完成了
making my frames the last one that i was
让我的画框成为我的最后一个
going to make is this one right here
你要做的就是这个吗？
because the first one is already
因为第一个已经是
represented by this one right here so
由这里的这位代表，所以
now we have all of our individual frames
现在我们有了所有的个人框架
let me zoom out a little bit so you can
让我把镜头放大一点，这样你就可以
see it better
看得更清楚些
once we are finished making our frames
一旦我们完成了镜框的制作
what we want to do is group them all
我们想要做的是将它们全部分组
together individually so i'm going to
单独在一起，所以我要去
click and drag over this one and i'm
点击并拖动到这个上面，我就会
going to group it instead of going to
要对其进行分组，而不是
object and selecting group an easier way
对象，并以更轻松的方式选择组
to do this would be to just press
要这样做，只需按下
control g on the keyboard so control g
键盘上的控件g，因此可以控制g
click and drag over this one ctrl g
在此ctrl g上单击并拖动
ctrl g and you get the id i'm just going
按Ctrl键，然后你拿到我要去的ID
through and grouping these one by one
逐一对它们进行整理和分组
and we want to make sure that these are
我们想要确保这些是
grouped so that when we batch export it
分组，以便在我们批量导出它时
they will all be their own individual
他们都将成为他们自己的个体
elements each frame
每帧元素
okay so
好的，那么
now i'm going to close out of the align
现在我要关闭队形了
distribute menu what i want now is the
分发菜单我现在想要的是
layers menu so over here where it says
Layers菜单，所以在这里它说
view objects
查看对象
click that button right there keyboard
点击键盘上的那个按钮
shortcut control shift and l
快捷键Shift与L
and if i click on these objects you'll
如果我点击这些物体，你会发现
notice that they highlight as they
请注意，它们高亮显示为
select them so i'm going to click on
选择它们，这样我就可以点击
this one right here and as you can see
这个就在这里，正如你所看到的
what's highlighted is this
突出显示的是以下内容
this label right here i want to change
这个标签我想换一下
the name of this from whatever this is
不管这是什么，这东西的名字
to the number one because this is the
第一名，因为这是
first frame in our sequence let me
我们序列中的第一帧让我
double click that i'm going to change it
双击我要更改它
to one
一比一
and press enter
并按Enter键
i'll click on this one this is frame
我会点击这个，这是相框
number two and this one is what's
第二个，这个是什么
highlighted so i'll click on that and
突出显示，所以我将点击它并
change that to two
换成两张吧。
press enter
按Enter键
i'll change this one to three
我要把这个换成三个。
four
四
five
五
six
六
seven
七
and eight
和八个
and if you're having trouble seeing
如果你有视力障碍
which layer you have selected sometimes
您有时选择了哪一层
if you're working with a complicated
如果您使用的是一个复杂的
animation you're going to have lots of
你会看到很多动画片
different layers and different frames
不同的层和不同的框架
going on here you might have to scroll
在这里，你可能需要滚动
up and down through this list here if
在此列表中上下移动，如果
you have a lot of items to figure out
你有很多东西要弄清楚
which which it is that you have selected
你选择的是哪一个
so once we've finished doing that we've
所以，一旦我们完成了这项工作，我们就
and drag over all of these objects right
并将其拖到所有这些对象上
here
这里
and now what i want to do is open up the
现在我想要做的是打开
export menu i will go to file and i will
导出菜单我会去归档，我会
select export
选择导出
now in this menu we want to choose batch
现在，在此菜单中，我们要选择批处理
export and we want to make sure we have
出口，我们希望确保我们有
selection we have these three different
选择我们有这三种不同的
options we have layer selection and
选项我们有层选择和
pages we want to choose selections now
我们现在要选择的页面
by default if you have all of these
默认情况下，如果您拥有所有这些
selected you should see it's all ready
选中后，您应该会看到一切都准备好了
to go right here we have these check
要去这里，我们有这些支票
boxes here one two three four it's not
箱子在这里，一二三四，不是
in order but that's okay it doesn't have
有秩序，但没关系，它没有
to be
成为
and now what i'm going to do is i'm
现在我要做的是
going to choose a place on my computer
要在我的电脑上选择一个地方
to export these two i'm just going to
要输出这两个，我只需要
put these on my desktop click this
把这些放在我的桌面上点击这里
i'm just going to put this on my desktop
我要把这个放到我的桌面上
and i'm going to name this
我要把这个命名为
i'm just going to name this spinner
我要把这个旋转器命名为
click save
点击保存
leave these defaults as they are and
保留这些默认设置不变，并
click ok and then it will export all of
单击确定，然后它将导出所有
those individually
那些单独的
and they should all be there now on your
他们现在应该都在你的电脑上
desktop so now it's time to open up
桌面，现在是开放的时候了
so that we can turn this into an
这样我们就可以把它变成一个
let me open up
让我敞开心扉
want to do is go to file and select open
要做的是转到文件并选择打开
graphics spinner one two three four so
图形微调器一二三四So
of these so i'm gonna select it hold
所以我要选择它保持
shift and click on all of these so that
按住Shift键并单击所有这些选项，以便
and go to open
然后去开张
now this may take a second because it
这可能需要一秒钟的时间，因为它
has to open up each of these individual
必须打开这些个体中的每一个
images one by one as you see it doing
当你看到它在做的时候，一个接一个的图像
here so give it a second to do its thing
在这里，所以给它一秒钟做它的事情
as you numbered them like i demonstrated
就像我演示的那样，你给他们编号
in the export portion of the lesson they
在本课的输出部分中，他们
should open up an order like that and
应该开一份这样的订单
now what you can do is you can just
现在你能做的就是
export this as an animated gif so let's
将其导出为动画gif，因此让我们
go to file and go to export as
转到文件并转到导出为
and i'm going to title this
我要把这件事命名为
i'm just going to name this spinner
我要把这个旋转器命名为
and over here where it says select file
在这里，上面写着选择文件
type i'm going to choose
我要选择的类型
gif image and click export
GIF图像，然后单击导出
now this parts really important uh
现在这个部分非常重要，嗯
you're going to get this menu that pops
你会看到这份弹出的菜单
up make sure where it says as animation
确定它说的是动画的地方
make sure you have this enabled by
确保您已通过以下方式启用此功能
default when you open up this will
默认情况下，打开此文件时将
be deselected if you don't have this
如果您没有此选项，请取消选择
selected it's just going to export it as
选中后，它只会将其导出为
a static image make sure you have that
一张静态图像确保你有
selected right there and this right here
在这里选择，在这里选择
delay between frames were unspecified in
帧之间的延迟未在中指定
milliseconds i think by default it's 200
毫秒，我想默认是200秒
now um the number that you should put
现在，嗯，你应该把这个数字
here depends on your graphic but for
这里取决于您的图形，但对于
this spinner graphic i'm just going to
下面我要介绍的微调图形
use 100
使用100
if you if you use this number and you
如果你使用这个号码，而你
find out it's too fast or the animation
找出它太快了，否则动画
is too slow you can always go back and
太慢了，你总是可以回到过去
change this number later on so i'm going
稍后更改这个号码，这样我就走了
to i'm just going to leave it at 100
我只想把它留在100
press export
冲压出口
and if i go to my desktop it should
如果我打开我的桌面，它应该
be there
一定要在那里
let me get out of there
让我离开那里
where is uh
嗯，在哪里？
spinner.gif there we go
旋转器。如果我们走了
it's gonna open this up and there you go
它会把这个打开，然后你就可以了
now we have our spinning our little
现在我们有了我们的小旋律
loading spinner
加载微调控制按钮
animation that we created with inkscape
我们使用Inkscape创建的动画
and with so
如果是这样的话
i think that should do it for this
我想这就够了。
tutorial that is how you can create
这就是您如何创建
simple animated gifs using inkscape if
使用Inkscape If的简单动画gif
you found this lesson useful then
你觉得这一课很有用吗？
consider checking out my inkscape master
考虑一下我的Inkscape大师
class it's a collection of over 60
班级它是一个超过60个人的集合
videos where i go over all of the tools
我浏览了所有工具的视频
and features in inkscape and i explain
和Inkscape中的功能，我解释
what they are and demonstrate how they
它们是什么并演示它们如何
work kind of like how i did in this
就像我在这件事上做的那样
video we even have a private community
视频我们甚至有一个私人社区
where you can ask questions and get help
您可以在那里提出问题并获得帮助
from me anytime you want i'll have some
你想随时从我这里来我都会有一些
information about that in the
有关此的信息在
description of the video if you want to
如果您想的话，可以描述视频
check that out as always thanks for
一如既往地检查一下谢谢
watching
看
[Music]
[音乐]